export default questions = [
	{
		title: "Gaming",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: "What company produces the PlayStation line of consoles?",
				answer: "Sony",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What Video Game surpassed Tetris to become the best-selling game of all time?",
				answer: "Minecraft",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question: "In what year was the Nintendo Wii released?",
				answer: "2006",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					'The first "Console War" was between the Super Nintendo Entertainment System and which Sega console?',
				answer: "The Sega Genesis/Mega Drive",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What launch title of the Nintendo Entertainment System saved the gaming industry in 1985?",
				answer: "Super Mario Bros.",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Browsers",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What proprietary Apple browser's name comes from a word for a hunting or exploration expedition?",
				answer: "Safari",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"Which browser was introduced as the default browser of Windows 10?",
				answer: "Microsoft Edge",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"Which browser is currently the most popular with over 60% of the market share?",
				answer: "Google Chrome",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"Which iconic web browser's 11th and final version finally stopped being supported in 2022?",
				answer: "Internet Explorer",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					'Which popular open-source browser was originally called "Phoenix"?',
				answer: "Mozilla Firefox",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "File Extensions",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question: "What is the file extension for plaintext documents?",
				answer: ".txt",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question: "What is the basic file extension for most webpages?",
				answer: ".html",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question: "What is the most common format for video files with audio?",
				answer: ".mp4",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question: "What common document format was invented by Abode in 1992?",
				answer: ".pdf",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What is the current main format of standard files created in Microsoft Excel?",
				answer: ".xlsx",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Hardware",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					"What type of USB port is commonly used to charge mobile devices?",
				answer: "USB-C (Type-C)",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question: "What does the acronym RAM stand for?",
				answer: "Random-Access Memory",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question:
					"What newer and faster storage hardware is currently replacing hard disk drives as the standard?",
				answer: "Solid State Drives (SSD)",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question:
					"Which computer component often causes a burning smell when it malfunctions?",
				answer: "Power Supply",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"What is the most common type of cable connects storage drives to other hardware components?",
				answer: "SATA Cable (Serial AT Attachment)",
			},
		],
	},
	{
		title: "Software",
		questions: [
			{
				points: 100,
				question:
					'Typing "cmd" into the search bar of a Windows device opens up which program?',
				answer: "command prompt",
			},
			{
				points: 200,
				question:
					"What file archiving software is associated with compressed files with the .7z extension?",
				answer: "7-zip",
			},
			{
				points: 300,
				question: "What is the name of the default test editor in Windows 10?",
				answer: "Notepad",
			},
			{
				points: 400,
				question: "What is the primary spreadsheet software of Apple products?",
				answer: "Numbers",
			},
			{
				points: 500,
				question:
					"Which picture editing software's name has become synonymous with edited images?",
				answer: "Adobe Photoshop",
			},
		],
	},
];
